<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="faq_title">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q1">Q: Do I need root access to use AmnShield AppControl?</string>
    <string name="faq_a1">A: No! AmnShield AppControl uses the Android VPN service to monitor and control internet traffic without requiring root access. This makes it safer and easier to use.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q2">Q: Is my data safe and private?</string>
    <string name="faq_a2">A: Yes. AmnShield AppControl is open source, contains no tracking, and all data is processed locally on your device. We do not collect or send any personal information to external servers.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q3">Q: Can I use AmnShield AppControl with other VPN apps?</string>
    <string name="faq_a3">A: No. Android does not allow running multiple VPN services simultaneously. You must disable other VPN apps or VPN profiles to use AmnShield AppControl.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q4">Q: How do I know which apps have internet access?</string>
    <string name="faq_a4">A: Check the color indicators next to each app. Green/Teal = access allowed, Red/Orange = access denied. Tap an app to see detailed access information.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q5">Q: Can I allow an app only on Wi-Fi?</string>
    <string name="faq_a5">A: Yes. You can set different rules for Wi-Fi and mobile networks. Tap the Wi-Fi and mobile icons separately for each app to configure this.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q6">Q: What is Blacklist vs Whitelist mode?</string>
    <string name="faq_a6">A: Blacklist (default) allows all apps except those you block. Whitelist blocks all apps except those you allow. Choose based on your preference in Settings.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q7">Q: Why is the app using battery?</string>
    <string name="faq_a7">A: The firewall needs to run continuously to monitor and control network traffic. However, it\'s optimized for minimal battery impact and can actually save battery by blocking unnecessary background connections.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q8">Q: Can I see what data apps are sending?</string>
    <string name="faq_a8">A: Yes. Enable detailed logging in Settings to see all network connections. Export logs to analyze traffic in detail.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q9">Q: What if the app crashes or doesn\'t respond?</string>
    <string name="faq_a9">A: Try restarting the app or your device. Check Settings to ensure everything is configured correctly. Report issues with detailed information if the problem persists.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q10">Q: Is AmnShield AppControl free?</string>
    <string name="faq_a10">A: Yes. AmnShield AppControl is completely free and open source. All features are available at no cost.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q11">Q: How do I uninstall AmnShield AppControl?</string>
    <string name="faq_a11">A: Simply uninstall like any other app. The VPN connection will be automatically disabled. All settings and logs will be removed.</string>
    
    <string name="faq_q12">Q: Can I export my logs?</string>
    <string name="faq_a12">A: Yes. Go to Settings and look for Export/Backup options to save your logs and configuration for analysis or backup purposes.</string>
</resources>
